Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Buttons and Memorabilia Collection, 1940-1990 IBT0057
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Miscellaneous Acquisitions, 1872-2013; Series 4
  - Lapel Pins, ca.1900-2011; Series 4 Subseries 2
    - U.S.P.O. Post Office Department Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 201)
    - Teamsters & American Flag Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 202a-202cc)
    - IBT Auto Transporters Division Lapel Pin, 2006; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 203)
    - IBT Airline Division Lapel Pin, 2006; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 204)
    - IBT Freight Division Lapel Pin, 2006; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 205)
    - IBT Port Division Lapel Pin, 2006; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 206)
    - IBT Rail Conference Lapel Pin, 2006; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 207)
    - IBT Dairy Conference Lapel Pin, 2006; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 208)
    - IBT Newspaper, Magazine & Electronic Media Workers Lapel Pin, 2006; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 209)
    - IBT Bakery & Laundry Conference, USA & Canada Lapel Pin, 2006; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 210)
    - IBT Industrial Trades Division Lapel Pin, 2006; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 211)
    - IBT Graphic Communications Conference Lapel Pin, 2006; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 212)
    - IBT Motion Picture & Theatrical Trade Division Lapel Pin, 2006; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 213)
    - IBT Buildign Materials & Construction Lapel Pin, 2006; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 214)
    - IBT Tankhaul Division Lapel Pin, 2006; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 215)
    - IBT Warehouse Division, 2006; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 216)
    - IBT Food Processing Division Lapel Pin, 2006; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 217)
    - IBT Convention Center & Tradeshow Division, 2006; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 218)
    - IBT Parcel & Small Package Lapel Pin, 2006; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 219)
    - Local 620 "Madison NJ, The Rose City" Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 219.5)
    - Teamsters 2006 Lapel Pin Sheet, Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Item 16)
    - Team Drivers International Union Lapel Pin, ca. 1900; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 111a-b)
    - IBT White, Blue, and Red Enameled Shield Lapel Pin, ca. 1903; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 112a-d)
    - "TLPA - 4" Cloverleaf Logo with Handshake (AFL-CIO Logo?) on a Blue Enamel Lapel Pin, ca. 1900-1920; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 113)
    - Teamsters National Union of America Blue Enamel Lapel Pins, ca. 1901; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 114a-d)
    - Team Drivers International Union Lapel Pin, ca. 1900; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 115)
    - "Presser '86" Lapel Pins, 1986; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 116a-c)
    - "'89 Preakness Celebration" Lapel Pin, 1989; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 117)
    - Eastern Conference of Teamsters 40th Anniversary Lapel Pin, 1993; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 118a-e)
    - Clinton/Gore 1996 Lapel Pin, Series 4 (Box 9, Item 119)
    - Kerry for President Lapel Pin, 2004; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 120)
    - IBT Warehouse Division 2001 Las Vegas Convention Lapel Pin, Series 4 (Box 9, Item 121)
    - 2001 IBT Convention Lapel Pins, Series 4 (Box 9, Item 122a-d)
    - Local 665 100 Year Anniversary Lapel Pin, 2003; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 123)
    - Local 135 100th Anniversary Lapel Pin, 2003; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 124)
    - Hoffa/Teamsters 2006 Harley-Davidson Logo, Series 4 (Box 9, Item 125)
    - Local 135 80 Year Anniversary Lapel Pins, 2008; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 126a-d)
    - Local 2 Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 127)
    - Local 2 Montana State Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 128a-b)
    - Food Processing Division - 28th IBT Convention Lapel Pin, 2011; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 129a-b)
    - Carhaul Division - 28th IBT Convention Lapel Pin, 2011; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 130a-b)
    - Warehouse Division - 28th IBT Convention Lapel Pin, 2011; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 131a-b)
    - Newspaper Division - 28th IBT Convention Lapel Pin, 2011; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 132a-b)
    - Industrial Trades Division - 28th IBT Convention Lapel Pin, 2011; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 133a-b)
    - Rail Division - 28th IBT Convention Lapel Pin, 2011; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 134a-b)
    - Tankhaul Division - 28th IBT Convention Lapel Pin, 2011; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 135a-b)
    - Port Division - 28th IBT Convention Lapel Pin, 2011; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 136a-b)
    - Airline Division - 28th IBT Convention Lapel Pin, 2011; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 137a-b)
    - BMCTD Division - 28th IBT Convention Lapel Pin, 2011; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 138a-b)
    - GCC/IBT Division - 28th IBT Convention Lapel Pin, 2011; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 139a-b)
    - Express Division - 28th IBT Convention Lapel Pin, 2011; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 140a-b)
    - Tradeshow Division - 28th IBT Conference Lapel Pin, 2011; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 141a-b)
    - Waste Division - 28th IBT Conference Lapel Pin, 2011; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 142a-b)
    - Brewery/Soft Drink Division - 28th IBT Conference Lapel Pin, 2011; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 143a-b)
    - Motion Picture Division - 28th IBT Conference Lapel Pin, 2011; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 144a-b)
    - Public Services Division - 28th IBT Conference Lapel Pin, 2011; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 145a-b)
    - Package Division - 28th IBT Conference Lapel Pin, 2011; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 146a-b)
    - Rail Division - 28th IBT Conference Lapel Pin, 2011; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 147)
    - Human Rights Division - 28th IBT Conference Lapel Pin, 2011; Series 4 (Box 9, Item data_value_missing_080f3b0686e76c176be63c2603b770ae)
    - Dairy Division - 28th IBT Conference Lapel Pin, 2011; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 149)
    - Freight - 28th IBT Conference Lapel Pin, 2011; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 150a-b)
    - Local 24 10 Year Membership Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 151)
    - Local 190 "Big Sky Country" Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 152a-b)
    - Local 190 "Billings, MT" Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 153)
    - Local 237 Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 154)
    - Local 299 Steward Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 155)
    - Local 362 IBT Logo Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 156a-c)
    - Local 364 Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 157)
    - Easatern Conference of Teamsters Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 158a-e)
    - Western Conference of Teamsters Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 159)
    - Central Conference of Teamsters Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 160)
    - Teamsters Construction Division Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 161)
    - Teamsters Airline Division Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 162a-d)
    - Teamsters ALD (Airline Division) Committee Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 163)
    - Teamsters Airline Division Pegasus Logo Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 164)
    - Teamsters Freight Division Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 165)
    - Teamsters Public Employees Division Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 166)
    - Teamsters Public Services Division Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 167a-b)
    - Teamsters Industrial Trades Division Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 168)
    - IBT Newspaper, Magazine, Electronic Media Division Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 169)
    - Teamsters Pipeliners Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 170)
    - IBT Warehouse Division Forklift Logo Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 171a-b)
    - IBT Warehouse Division Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 172)
    - Teamsters Port Division Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 173)
    - IBT Safety and Health Department Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 174a-c)
    - IBT/Hard Hat Logo BM & CTD Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 175)
    - Black Enamel 10 Year Membership Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 176)
    - Black Enamel 15 Year Membership Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 177)
    - White and Blue Enamel 15 Year Membership Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 178)
    - White and Blue Enamel 20 Year Membership Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 179)
    - Black Enamel 20 Year Membership Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 180)
    - Blue and White Enamel 25 Year Membership Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 181)
    - Blue and White Enamel Version 2 25 Year Membership Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 182)
    - Black Enamel 25 Year Membership Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 183)
    - Blue and White Enamel 30 Year Membership Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 184)
    - Blue and White Enamel Version 2 30 Year Membership Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 185)
    - Blue and White Enamel 35 Year Membership Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 186)
    - 50 Year Membership Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 187)
    - "I.B. of T. C. W. & H. of A./ AF of L/ Reigstered" IBT Logo Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 188a-b)
    - Teamsters Local Education Coordinator Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 189)
    - Teamsters Logo "Retiree" Lapel Pin - Version 1, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 190a-b)
    - Teamsters Logo "Retiree" Lapel Pin - Version 2, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 191)
    - Teamsters Logo "Retiree" Lapel Pin - Version 3, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 192a-c)
    - Teamsters Logo Steward Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 193)
    - Teamsters D.R.I.V.E. Circular Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 194a-c)
    - Teamsters D.R.I.V.E. Truck Shaped Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 195)
    - Teamsters D.R.I.V.E. Black Enamel Capital Building Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 196a-e)
    - Teamsters D.R.I.V.E. Black Enamel Capital Building Lapel Pins with Blue/Yellow Member Cards, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 197a-b)
    - Teamsters D.R.I.V.E. Black Enamel Capital Building Lapel Pins with Blue/Yellow Member Cards, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 198a-b)
    - "I.B. of T. C. S. & H. of A." Logo Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 199)
    - Black Enamel Teamsters Logo Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 200)
    - Silver Teamsters Logo Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 201)
    - IBT Logo w/ Regional Conferences Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 202)
    - Blue/White Enamel and Gold IBT Logo Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 203a-g)
    - Teamsters Women Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 204a-b)
    - "Hoffa/Hogan Restore the Pride" Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 205)
    - "A Friend of Hoffa" Truck Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 206a-e)
    - National Safety Council 2 Year Safe Driver Award Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 207)
    - National Safety Council 3 Year Safe Driver Award Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 208)
    - National Safety Council 4 Year Safe Driver Award Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 209)
    - National Safety Council 9 Year Safe Driver Award Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 210)
    - National Safety Council 13 Year Safe Driver Award Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 211)
    - National Safety Council 14 Year Safe Driver Award Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 212)
    - National Safety Council 15 Year Safe Driver Award Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 213)
    - National Safety Council 16 Year Safe Driver Award Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 214)
    - "1 Year Without Accident Ace Driver - Markel Service" Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 215a-b)
    - 2 Year Safe Driver - Buckeye Union Casualty Co. Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 216)
    - IKE Safety Award - 3 Years Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 217)
    - 50,000 Mile Safe Driving Club Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 218)
    - U.S. Truck Lines Safety League Award, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 219a-b)
    - "Service for Security" Indiana National Guard Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 220)
    - Freightliner Trucks Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 221)
    - American Trucking Association (ATA) 8 Year Safe Driving Award Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 222)
    - Embroidered Fabric - Aviator Wings (?) Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 223)
    - US Military Parachutist Badge, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 224)
    - Golden Spike Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 225a-b)
    - "A. of M." Carpenter's Square and Compass (?) Freemason (?) Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 226)
    - "VA Research and Development" Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 227)
    - "Compliments of K & R Industries" American Flag Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 228)
    - Square Magnetic IBT Logo Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 229a-e)
    - Jeweled Bronze IBT Logo Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 230a-c)
    - Jeweled Gold IBT Logo Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 231a-e)
    - Small Gold/Silver IBT Logo Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 232a-f)
    - Navy Blue Enamel IBT Logo Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 233a-f)
    - Small IBT Logo "Registered" Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 234a-d)
    - Small IBT Logo Matte Gold "Registered" Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 235a-e)
    - Large Blue and White Enamel IBT Logo "Registered" Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 236a-f)
    - American Flag/IBT Logo Flag Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 237a-e)
    - Sky Blue Enamel IBT Logo Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 238)
    - IBT Logo Lapel Pin with Blue/Red/White Ribbon, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 239)
    - Bastian Brothers IBT Logo Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 240a-b)
    - "The Teamster Emblem - A Mark of Distinction - Wear it Proudly" Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 241a-b)
    - Bastian Brothers IBT Logo Lapel Pins w/out Paper Backin, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 242a-c)
    - "The Teamster Emblem" Lapel Pins w/out Paper Backing, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 243a-c)
  - Material Collected by Hollis Hypes, 1934-1969; Series 4 Subseries 3
    - Local 42 (Jul 1934) Button, Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Item 220)
    - P. & C. H. D., T., H. & W. Kanas City, MO & Vicinity (Dec 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Item 221)
    - Local 814 (Jul 1941) Button, Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Item 222)
    - Local 690 (Feb 1944) Button, Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Item 223)
    - Local 246 Steward Button, 1959; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Item 224)
    - Local 705 (Jul, Aug, Sep 1969) Button, Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Item 225)
    - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers UNITE Button, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Item 226)
    - DRIVE Van-Shaped Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Item 227)
    - IBT Logo Small "Registered" Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Item 228)
    - Local 365 Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Item 229)
    - DRIVE to Survive Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Item 230)
    - DRIVE to Survive Truck-Shaped Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Item 231)
    - Int'l Ladies Garment Workers Union small pleather pouch, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Item 232)
    - 1961 18th IBT Convention Postcard, Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Item 233)
  - Material Collected by Sue Mauren, 1978-2006; Series 4 Subseries 4
    - Don Peters International Vice-President Button, 1978; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 234)
    - Maurice R. Schurr International Vice-President Button, 1978; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 235)
    - Re-Elect Ray Schoessling General Secy.-Treas. Button, 1981; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 236)
    - Joint Council 25 Ray, Roy & Louie Buttons, 1981; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 237a-b)
    - Go "Jackie" Gen'l. President Button, 1983; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 238)
    - "Jackie" Presser for Int'l Vice-Pres. Button, 1983; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 239)
    - "I'm a Teamster for Perpich and Berg" Button, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 240)
    - Louie Peick Int'l Vice-Pres. Button, 1981; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 241)
    - IBT Unity Team R.V. Durham for General President Button, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 242)
    - R.V. Durham Unity Team Button, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 243)
    - R.V. Durham Unity Team Larry Brennan Button, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 244)
    - R.V. Durham Unity Team Louis Lacroix Button, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 245)
    - "R. V. Durham Says: No Gov't, No MOB, No TDU, No B__S__!" Button, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 246)
    - "Don't Blame Me I Voted for R.V." Button, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 247)
    - R.V. Durham Unity Team Robert T. Simpson Button, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 248)
    - "I Support R.V. Durham" Button, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 249)
    - "Support 55 Senate File" Solidarity Day Button, Minnesota Drive, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 250)
    - "No Scabs" Solidarity Day, Minnesota Drive Button, 1991; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 251)
    - "Hoffa '96" Button, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 252)
    - Hoffa, Hogan, Flynn '96 Button, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 253)
    - "Teamsters Vote Hoffa/Keegel '96" Button, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 254)
    - "Hoffa '96 Restore the Power" Button, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 255)
    - "I'm a Friend of Jimmy Hoffa" Button, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 256)
    - "Hoffa-Malinsky Restore the Pride" Button, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 257)
    - "Teamsters Vote Hoffa/Keegel '98" Button, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 258)
    - "Hoffa 2006" Button, Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 259)
    - "New England Teamsters for McCarthy Vote Roy and Ray and the Team" Buttons, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 260a-b)
    - "Roy Williams No. 1" Button, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 261)
    - "...And Justice For All, Even Teamsters" Button, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 262)
    - "Respect is a Teamster Contract" Button, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 263)
    - "Joe 'T' for You and Me!" Button, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 264)
    - "Teamsters Steward Local 543" Button, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 265)
    - "If You Want It, Fight For It!" Local 995 Button, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 266)
    - "You Can Bet on Jackie & Weldon" 23rd International IBT Convention Poker Chip, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 267)
    - Local 135 "John Neal, President/Danny L. Barton Secretary-Treasurer" Keychain, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 268)
    - "Union Yes Local 221" Deck of Cards, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 269)
    - "Central Conference of Teamsters" Plastic Disc, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 270)
    - "T.J.C. No. 32 Minnesota" Teamsters Logo Embroidered Patch, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 271)
    - "Minnesota Teamsters" Embroidered Patch, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 272)
    - Teamsters Logo Canadian/American Flag Embroidered Patch, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 273)
    - "Central Conference Public Employee Division" Embroidered Patch, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 274)
    - "Teamsters Law Enforcement" Local 726 Embroidered Patch, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 275)
    - Local 705 Teamsters Logo Embroidered Patch, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 276)
    - "Vote Roy L. Williams General President I.B.T." Plastic Clip, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 4, Item 277)
  - Miscellaneous Memorabilia Items, 1903-2008; Series 4 Subseries 5
    - Local 470 Teamsters Logo Embroidered Patch, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 4, Item 278)
    - "100 Years of Quality Service, The American Linen Family of Companies" Embroidered Patch, 1989; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 4, Item 279)
    - "Teamsters Wildcat 1970" Embroidered Patch, Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 4, Item 280)
    - "Variety Club" Embroidered Patch, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 4, Item 281)
    - "National Champions P&D Safety Roadway" Embroidered Patch, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 4, Item 282)
    - "Roadway" Embroidered Patch, Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 4, Item 283)
    - "Mid-American Truck Lines, Inc." Embroidered Patch, Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 4, Item 284)
    - Teamsters/Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers & Trainmen Sticker, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 4, Item 285)
    - "Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees Division" IBT Logo Sticker, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 4, Item 286)
    - C.I.O. First Constitutional Convention Medal, Pittsburgh 1938, R. A. Tobin Attendee, Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 4, Item 287)
    - IBT Logo "Registered" Tie Clips, Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 4, Item 288a-b)
    - "R. Emmett Kelly Bldg. Oct. 28, 1979" UFCW Keychain, Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 4, Item 289)
    - IBT Logo "Registered" Small Medallion/Keychain Piece, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 4, Item 290)
    - Local 82 75th Anniversary Truck Shaped-Keychain, 2008; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 4, Item 291)
    - Local 690 IBT Logo Keychain, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 4, Item 292)
    - S. E. Bennet Company/Teamsters Logo Keychain, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 4, Item 293)
    - Local 251 Keychain, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 4, Item 294)
    - IBT Logo "Registered" Keychain, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 4, Item 295)
    - IBT Logo Money Clip, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 4, Item 296)
    - IBT Logo Bolo Tie, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 4, Item 297)
    - Teamsters Local #2 (Butte, MT) Neoprene Cup Sleeves, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 4, Item 298a-c)
    - "Hoffa - Past, Present, Future" Model Freight Truck, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 5, Item 1)
    - Joint Council 13 "1911-2011" Anniversary Plastic Cup and Neoprene Cozy, Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 5, Item 2a-b)
    - Local 25, Boston MA IBT Logo Watch, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 5, Item 3)
    - Local 52 IBT Logo Watch, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 5, Item 4)
    - Gold IBT Logo/Jimmy Hoffa Watch, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 5, Item data_value_missing_f72073422384c6f4570ad50c06ee40ba)
    - DRIVE for Victory American Flag Framed Sticky Decal, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 5, Item 6)
    - Local 135 Deck of Cards, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 244a-b)
    - Local 404 Operative Plasterers' and Cement Masons' International Association Key Chain, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 245)
    - Hoffa 2006 Key Chain, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 246)
    - IBT Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees Division Leather Keychain, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 247)
    - Toledo Teamsters Federal Credit Union Key Chain, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 248)
    - IBT Logo Red White and Blue '76 Key Chain, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 249)
    - J.R.H.M.S.F. Golf Divot Tool, 2008; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 250)
    - Teamsters Local 2000 Key Chains, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 251a-b)
    - Local 507 Keychains, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 252a-b)
    - IBT Logo Gold and Blue Enamel Keychain (Large), Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 253)
    - IBT Logo Gold and Blue Enamel Keychain (Small), Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 254)
    - IBT TITAN Small Metal Plaque, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 255)
    - "Joe Dwyer Local 1064" Metal Badge, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 256)
    - James R. Hoffa Memorial Scholarship Fund Drive for Education Plastic Plaque, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 257)